<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gamed-peer-review on Michael Healy</title>
    <link>https://michaelhealy.space/series/gamed-peer-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gamed-peer-review on Michael Healy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Michael Healy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 06:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://michaelhealy.space/series/gamed-peer-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusions</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-conclusions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 06:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-conclusions/</guid>
      <description>This is an idea that is relatively new, but I think there is great promise in it. Working through the process of performing the revision narrative has been an interesting one. Its one that I knew wouldn&amp;#8217;t be easy, but has also proven to be more difficult than I had at first imagined.
[aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img_0415-e1462474741733.jpg&amp;amp;#8221; name=&amp;#8221;Process&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;left&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;40%&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]
&amp;nbsp;
The first thing has been purely logistical. In performing this on my WordPress site, I have had flexibility to move and connect things as I would like, to relate posts together through smart linking and decision trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 06:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-integration/</guid>
      <description>You open up healy.gwp.draft2.
  [aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img_0406.jpg&amp;#8221; name=&amp;#8221;Revision&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;center&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;100%&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]  It&amp;#8217;s time to get serious with this article! There are a number of reasons for your wanting to do this. First, you really like this idea, think it has great potential, works with your interests, and you&amp;#8217;ve had some luck using it in your own classrooms. In fact, this semester the workshop quest seemed to work really well for a number of your students, with them starting to better see the connections between peer-review and their work, both as readers and as writers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serious Revisions</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-serious-revisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 06:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-serious-revisions/</guid>
      <description>You stare at the open document. You&amp;#8217;ve pulled together quotes and research notes. The weight of doing the revisions in situ seem overwhelming. You open a new document, title it Literature Review, and start typing.
You start with the major moves that you&amp;#8217;ve seen in connecting to your own work. You create a set of bullet points that lay out your thoughts and the themes you see.
 Process and Revision Peer-Review and Troubles Workshop as a collaborative and process space Multimodality/Literacy/Connections between Peer-Review, Workshop, Gaming Gamification as a Method of Connecting Process, Peer-Review, and Collaboration in the Workshop  Once you&amp;#8217;ve laid it out and see the major moves, you start typing away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gamed Process Narrative</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-the-gamed-process-narrative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 05:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-the-gamed-process-narrative/</guid>
      <description>Within this particular pedagogy students are asked to go back through their writing process and to create an interactive revision text. This is set up as a way for students to think about and play with memory. It is a way for them to engage with their writing in their memory as they account for how it came into being. There are a few pieces of this assignment that seem important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 05:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-09-run/</guid>
      <description>You lace up your shoes, your new shoes, the Altra Torin 2.0s. The ones you just got last week. The ones that feel good in the way that only new shoes can. You head out into the neighborhood, your work on the tip of your mind. You click your watch to record the miles and head out.
You return home after about a 30-45 minutes, somewhere between 3 and 5 miles done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revise Literature Review</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-revise-literature-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-revise-literature-review/</guid>
      <description>You stare at the literature review section of your article. This is one section that you really need to revise. It is unclear what work you&amp;#8217;ve done, what the gap is, and how you fit in. Come on Michael, you can do this.
You open Evernote and locate your research notes. First you create a list with the movements of the research. You have questions like &amp;#8220;Why do peer review?&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;Why is it difficult?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading and Research</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-reading-and-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-reading-and-research/</guid>
      <description>Instead of doing any writing you choose to go back and do more research. You&amp;#8217;ve already read three books in relationship to this article by now. What else do you need? Oh well.
Hours later, and no further writing on your draft, you have a new stack of articles that seem related. You&amp;#8217;ve also thought about other potentials for revision, peer-review, creative writing, and multimodality that need researching.
You decide that you could research forever if you wanted to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Revision Narrative</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-more-revision-narrative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-more-revision-narrative/</guid>
      <description>Whoa, that was a lot of work. I hope that you haven&amp;#8217;t been lost. I&amp;#8217;ve often felt lost as I&amp;#8217;ve explored these areas, memories, and my own process. Now that that&amp;#8217;s out of the way, lets continue back on to adventure.
You rename the document &amp;#8220;healy.gwp.draft1&amp;#8221; and read through your work. There are some decent ideas here. You like what you&amp;#8217;ve done. However, given the reading, there is a big gap in the theory section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cast of Characters</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-cast-of-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-cast-of-characters/</guid>
      <description>[aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img_0406.jpg&amp;amp;#8221; name=&amp;#8221;Revision&amp;#8221; caption=&amp;#8221;Mardi, the mascot of revision. It is also fun to post pictures of the pup.&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;left&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;50%&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]
[aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/memory.jpg&amp;amp;#8221; name=&amp;#8221;Memory&amp;#8221; caption=&amp;#8221;The operator.&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;right&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;50%&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]
[aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img_0415-e1462474741733.jpg&amp;amp;#8221; name=&amp;#8221;Process&amp;#8221; caption=&amp;#8221;It&amp;#8217;s work, it takes time.&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;left&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;50%&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]
[aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img_0261.jpg&amp;amp;#8221; name=&amp;#8221;Gaming&amp;#8221; caption=&amp;#8221;The idea of gaming and play is important for the connections between memory and revision.&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;right&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;50%&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]
Follow on for key questions and background information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrance</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-entrance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-entrance/</guid>
      <description>You find yourself sitting in a room. There is a computer in front of you playing music. There is a cup of coffee on the desk.
You take a drink and start to type.
You&amp;#8217;ve been working on a piece that you&amp;#8217;ve titled: &amp;#8220;It’s Dangerous to Go Alone! Take This&amp;#8221;: Co-op Play and the Gamified Workshop.&amp;#8221; It&amp;#8217;s a piece that you&amp;#8217;ve been working on since taking Creative Writing Pedagogy last fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works Cited</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-works-cited/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-works-cited/</guid>
      <description>Aguilar, Stephen J., Caitlin Holman, and Barry J. Fishman. “Game-Inspired Design: Empirical Evidence in Support of Gameful Learning Environments.” Games and Culture (2015): 1-27. Web. Sage Journals.
Alexander, Jonathan. “Gaming, Student Literacies, and the Composition Classroom: Some Possibilities for Transformation.” College Composition and Communication 61.1 (2009): 35-63. Web. JSTOR.
Augustine. “The Confessions of Saint Augustine: Book X.” Web. Blackboard. Microsoft Word File.
Bailey, Wm. Ruffin. “Hacks, Mods, Easter Eggs, and Fossils: Intentionality and Digitalism in the Video Game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-literature-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 19:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-literature-review/</guid>
      <description>What has been said already?   Memory:   [aesop_character img=&amp;#8221;http://www.michaelhealy.info/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/memory.jpg&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;right&amp;#8221; width=&amp;#8221;400px&amp;#8221; force_circle=&amp;#8221;off&amp;#8221;]  I would like to start with a number of ideas with memory. The first is to go way back to Augustine and to the idea that memory is a generative force, that “when I speak, the images of all I speak of are present, out of the same treasury of memory; nor would I speak of any thereof, were the images wanting” (Augustine 5).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions and Background</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-questions-and-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 15:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-questions-and-background/</guid>
      <description>The germ of this idea was connecting revision and memory. How do we teach revision? How might we teach it better? How might working with memory help? I looked to Julie Jung, Jody Shipka, and Kathleen Blake Yancey to see what others have said.
I&amp;#8217;ve also had a fascination with gamification. I have my own history as a gamer, and specifically a computer gamer, that has informed many of these initial inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revision and Memory Definitions</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-revision-and-memory-definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 15:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/gamed_peer_review/2016-05-05-revision-and-memory-definitions/</guid>
      <description>An exploration of definitions: These are the definitions that I am working with in this project. They have been founded in rhetoric and composition, though many of them are my own synthesis of theory. They have informed the production of this project.
What is revision? Revision is a memory practice. Revision is a remembering strategy. Revision is recursive. Revision is a part of the writing process. Revision is a series of choices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>