<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent and Upcoming Presentations on Michael Healy</title>
    <link>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent and Upcoming Presentations on Michael Healy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Michael Healy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://michaelhealy.space/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>At Play with Composition: Explorations of Voice</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/samla2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/samla2017/</guid>
      <description>I am studying the efficacy of play as an organizational and pedagogical theory in ENC 2135. I am interested in students’ perceptions on play within the composition classroom, especially in the development of voice and agency in their writing. I have anecdotally seen it as a positive influence through my teaching, but I want something more empirical that I can build from.
To do the study I have prepared a material’s release form and a short survey to distribute to students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circulation, Narrative, and Human Rights: New Materialism meets Spectacular Rhetoric</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/femrhet2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/femrhet2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ludic Revision: Potential, Play, and Choice</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/cccc2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 21:47:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/cccc2017/</guid>
      <description>In examining intersections between creative writing and composition, revision stands out as “a space in which we teach students that they have choices” (Leahy and Dechow) as they “engag[e] in rigorous self-refection while reading and writing” (Jung). By further framing this revision as play, or ludic revision, we can help students envision the potential of their writing. Ludic revision is collaborative play with language, and it allows students to productively fail as they work through rhetorical choices in the revision process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Grandma: (Re)Making (or Appropriating?) Agency in the Archive</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/femrhet2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/talk/femrhet2015/</guid>
      <description>The full profile video available through the UNO Women&amp;rsquo;s Archive.   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>