<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ePortflio on Michael Healy</title>
    <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ePortflio on Michael Healy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Michael Healy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Letting the Language Lead: A Semester of Composition Theory</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/reflection/</guid>
      <description>Re-inhabiting Composition I’ve been re-inhabiting the perspectives project this last weekend, while also working on this reflection and having various levels of success baking bread. I was working with Jessi through the unedited video of the interview to transcribe and code a section of it for research methods. As I was listening again to what Ned Stuckey-French had to say about composition, composing, writing, tools, technologies, and teaching, there was a phrase that he used, “letting the language lead”, that stood out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triptych Plus Project</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/triptych/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/triptych/</guid>
      <description>Triptych 1: Homebrewing Beer I am examining the composing practices of the homebrew beer community, one that, while not an academic field, does serve as a discourse community. It is also one that I have been involved in for close to 10 years in different capacities. There are a number of different composing practices within the community, from the sharing of recipes and expertise in various forums, to the creation of recipes, to the composition of books, and the assemblage of recipes and recipe kits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspectives Project: Ned Stuckey-French</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/perspectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 20:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/perspectives/</guid>
      <description>Embedding the video here also allows me to do some additional contextual work. Much of what Ned Stuckey-French has written can be found at his website. He is someone, who in his responses and his writing, crosses many boundaries, and seems to invite others to do the same. His perspective is one of learning from students on writing and composing practices, seeing his work in the classroom as informing and influencing his own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SRR 3: Situating Composition Studies</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/selection1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/selection1/</guid>
      <description>These three pieces detail the historic movements, developments, and changes of composition as an action, pedagogy, theory, class, and concession. Skinnel details the evolution of composition classes at Arizona State as the college developed and changed over its history. Miller detail the development of College English through rhetoric and Belles Lettres in the Scottish system of higher education. Braddock examines the use of topic sentences within popular compositions with an aim at examining the ways in which we teach writing at the paragraph level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection 2: Blog Post, Processing Assumptions</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/selection2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 21:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/selection2/</guid>
      <description>Blog Post: Processing Assumptions So far, we have surveyed some of the historical nature of the field and the discipline, we have yet to see the theoretical march and progression through different theories and theoretical stances as they had developed. As I read, I was struck by how many of the same issues, problems, and assumptions have largely stayed the same or are still being wrestled with.
Rohman and Wlecke consider an early form of process pedagogy, where-in pre-writing “writing, as one form of creation, is more usefully though of not as made up of words, but of combinations of words” (224).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Program Acronyms: Considering Contexts, Systems, and Locales</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/selection3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 22:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/selection3/</guid>
      <description>David Russel examines the historical development of WAC/WID in modern American universities. Starts with the considerations of composition in universities as a very “American” sort of issue. Connects various waves of development to different “literacy crisis” as new populations of students entered into higher education. These developments roughly paralleled other interests in rhetoric and composition, with WAC/WID developing alongside growth in the study of writing, with emerging PhDs in rhetoric and composition eventually coming in to design and run these programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theories of Composition ePortfolio</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/</guid>
      <description>This is my Spring 2017 Composition Theory ePortfolio. The links go to the individual components that have been selected for inclusion. The selections here represent some of the work of this semester though is not inclusive. I also intend for these selections and reflections to look back to what I brought into the class, what I learned here, and forward to new contexts. At the bottom of this page are links to and brief descriptions of each artifact collected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Project Abstract</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 22:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/abstract/</guid>
      <description>For my final project I am proposing a conference concurrent-session presentation that uses research from my classroom this semester. I am studying the efficacy of play as an organizational and pedagogical theory in ENC 2135. I am interested in students; perceptions on play within the composition classroom, especially in the development of voice and agency in their writing. I have anecdotally seen it as a positive influence through my teaching, but I want something more empirical that I can build from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual Whack-a-Mole</title>
      <link>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/triptychreflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 17:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelhealy.space/project/eportfolios/comptheory/triptychreflection/</guid>
      <description>In looking back through my exploration of homebrewing, a SpaceX webcast, and Malea Powell’s CCCCs address, I see trends coalesce around the social nature of composing and composition. The different composing practices and compositions of these three artifacts are all situated in-between multiple voices, knowledges, places, spaces, and practices. Composition, from looking at these three pieces of the triptych, assembles into a communal inscription by a person or persons onto the world, with some specific and rhetorical aim to the process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>